# **Oleksandr Malinovskyi**

<u>+38 (066) 527 02 34</u>

malinovskiy.alexandr

malinovskiy.alexandr@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/alexander-malinovskiy

www.facebook.com/alexander.malinovskiy

### General info

Nationality: Ukrainian

Date of birth: July 6, 1986

Resident of: Ukraine
Marital status: single

# Summary:

Hello! I'm Oleksandr Malinovskyi. Junior Web Developer specializing in front-end development. Experienced with creating web pages from psd/sketch, familiar to different devices, fluid and responsive layout. Have a good background in project management, customer relations and work in team.

### **Education**

Mar 2017 - Jul 2017 Projector - Design & Development school, Kyiv.

Certificate of courses "Front-end. JavaScript. Basic."

Click to <u>view certificate</u>.

Mar 2016 – Jul 2016 Projector - Design & Development school, Kyiv.

Certificate of courses "Front-End. Basic. HTML/CSS."

Click to view certificate.



Sep 2003 – Jun 2009 National Aviation University, Kyiv.

Specialist of Automation and computer integrated complexes and processes.

## **Experience**

Apr 2017 – Jul 2017 Junior Front-End Developer at Coderiver, Kyiv.

About the Company: Web-studio specializing in Front-end development.

Jan 2011 – Apr 2017 Engineer by Introduction of New Technics and

Technologies at OptiVision LLC, Kyiv.

About the Company: Professional integrator of audio-visual equipment on objects of any complexity. The company provides a wide range of solutions in the field of AV: construction of advertising-information video networks (Digital Signage) basis of any display facilities, IPTV, videowalls, design video screens places of sales and entertainment centers, equipment visualization and audio systems of all types for commercial buildings, sport complexes, cinemas and concert halls, passenger terminals and situation centers, multimedia classrooms in schools, etc.

#### **Key Responsibilities:**

- Introduction AV products and technologies
- Hardware testing before installation
- Customizing equipment
- Commissioning
- Technical support
- Customers staff training
- Consulting
- Projects manager

### **Key projects:**

- OceanPlaza Mall, Kyiv Content Management System (Digital Signage) for Media Façade (2012), Interactive Digital Wayfinder system (2015).
- 2. Prospect Mall, Kyiv Interactive Digital Wayfinder system (2014).
- British American Tobacco, Pryluky Industrial TV system on the plant (2014 2015).
- 4. Silenza Lingerie Boutiques, Kyiv Network of videowalls and Interactive Assistants (2015).
- 5. Galnaftogaz Concern (OKKO) Digital Signage network for flagship gas stations including: Digital Menus, videowall and outdoor-displays (2015).
- 6. Delta Bank, Kyiv and regions Digital Signage network (2010 2012).
- 7. The main clock of country (Independence Square) Control System and Content management software (Digital Signage) to sync the four LED-screens (2011).

### **Technologies:**

- Digital Signage software (YCD, C-nario, Navori, FireCast, BroadSign, LiveBoard, etc.)
- Windows 7, Windows 8, Windows Server 2008 R2, Ubuntu 14.04, MySQL,
   LAN.
- RAdmin, RDP, TCP/IP, DHCP, software and drivers installation.
- Site administration (engine by Joomla CMS)

Oct 2007 – Dec 2010 Support Engineer & LED-screens Operator and Engineer of Rental Department at <u>EKTA LLC</u>, Kyiv.

About the Company: EKTA is a specialized technology company that develops, manufactures and provides system integration of indoor and outdoor LED display solutions for a variety of markets including DOOH media, branding, sports and events, television, corporate AV, leisure and entertainment, traffic and transportation.

#### **Key Responsibilities:**

LED-screens installation

**Equipment adjustment** 

Repair of the equipment

**Content management** 

Participated in (on-line, Live) TV-shows

Key TV projects: Fan-zone 2010 FIFA WORLR CUP, Svoboda slova (channel "ICTV"),

Shuster LIVE (2009, channel "Ukraine"), Fabrika Zirok (2007, channel "Novy"), Svoboda

na Interi (channel "Inter"), etc.

Apr 2006 – Aug 2007

**Network Engineer at provider BELICHI.NET.UA** 

(acquired by Lanet.ua), Kyiv.

About the Company: The main activities of the company are: provision of Internet

access services, data services and other related services for all types of users.

Specialized in provision of complete set of Internet network services, with subsequent

technical support. The Company provides high quality telecommunications solutions

by external channels and its own technical base.

**Key Responsibilities:** 

**Users** connection

Hardware installation

**Users support** 

Languages

**English: Intermediate** 

**Hobbies** 

Cycling, traveling, swimming, ping pong, bowling, parachuting, karting,

poker and mafia games together with my friends.